# Sofia Kasimi



#### Contact



sofiakasimiux@gmail.com



+45 71638102



SofiaUX/portfolio-website

#### Software

Adobe Suite / Creative Cloud Sketch / Figma / UX Pin

Invision / Studio

Atom / Github

Google Analytics / Hotjar

### Language

Greek
English
Dutch
Danish

## Hobby









## UX-UI Designer/ Frontend Designer

Creative UX Designer with experience in designing and developing real-world applications.

My graphic design coupled with the UI-UX skills gave me a holistic view of delivering user-centered designs, from the ideation to the polished deliverables, escalating usability with the firm identity.

Having applied knowledge in web front-end development, I understand systems and their limitations and I can drive puzzle-solving discussions.

#### Experience

2020-2020 (May-Sep) UX Designer at Wedio (short agreement) https://www.wedio.com/

- · Structure new feature "Dashboards"
- · Analyze and convert user traffic
- Prioritize the design tasks for development

2020-2020 (Jan-May)

UX/UI Designer at Webshipper https://webshipper.com/

- · Illustrate user inputs to Personas
- · Redesign the Saas platform
- Documented Modular UI library

2018-2019 (Sep-Dec)

UX Designer at St-Art B.V https://www.st-artamsterdam.com/

- Architect sitemap and user-journeys
- Design and test interactive mockups
- Conduct & analyze A/B testing to solutions

2012-2018 (Nov-Jun)

Freelancer Graphic Designer logo designer & book illustrator

- Logo design accompanied by Brand Book
- · Illustrate infographics for higher ranking

#### Education

2017-2018 (Feb-Jan)



UX specialist / Front end designer https://careerfoundry.com/

- · UX / UI responsive app from scratch
- · IA and UX research / discovery phase
- · Web app development (HTML, CSS, JS)

2007-2010 (Sep-Oct)

BA of Art / Graphic Design https://vakalo.gr/vakalo-college-english/